xiaomiadvices.com 2017-12-13

# Privacy Policy | Xiaomi Advices

The privacy of visitors to our site is important to us.

### Xiaomi Advices Respects your Privacy

Thanks for being one of our valued visitor at Xiaomi Advices. This page ([Xiaomi Advices](http://xiaomiadvices.com/) Privacy Policy) shows what type of personal information is collected, when visitor browse our site. We safeguard your personal information and never sell it with any third parties.

### Log Files

Similar to other www websites, Xiaomi Advices also collect and uses log files.  This files contain the information regarding IP (Internet Protocol) address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider), browser used by you to visit Xiaomi Advices, the time you spend and what pages you surf on our website. This files are used only for administration and maintenance purpose only.

Xiaomi Advices will never ask for your Debit or Credit Card details, so never submit on any of our website page.

### Third Party Advertising

We use Google Ads, Amazon, Viglink, Advertising.com, Media.net and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These advertising companies may use information (not including your name, email address, address or telephone number) about your visit to serve the best ads of your interest.

Looking for more information about such practices, refer below-

 _Google – http://www.google.com/privacy.html_

 _Sixapart – http://www.sixapart.com/privacy/_

 _Kontera – http://www.kontera.com/privacy.aspx_

 _Amazon – Amazon.com Privacy Notice_

 _Share A Sale – http://www.shareasale.com/w3c/policy.html_

 _Advertising –<http://advertising.aol.com/privacy>_

Other ads served in the Gadgets Academy are media.net, Amazon, advertising.com, Viglink, Infolinks and pop-cash also uses the cookies to track user’s activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness. In addition, we GadgetsAcademy has no control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers. You need not to accept cookies each time. You can also block or disable all cookies from your browser. These can be done through Settings options present on your browser.

### Links to External Websites

The sites which we link on our website for reference purpose are not associated with us. So there is no control on the nature of external websites. So make sure to read their privacy policy before disclosing your personal information.

### Flashing ROM

We at Xiaomi Advices share various tutorials to flash custom ROM and stock ROM on Android devices. The links to download this ROM are from third party Android developers websites, so we can’t assure you 100 % working of this files. Also proceed at your own risk whenever flashing a custom ROM or rooting your device. We should not held responsible for anything happens to your device.

### Trademarks

XiaomiAdvices.com is not affiliated with Google, Motorola, Sony, Xiaomi, Micromax, Samsung, Apple or any of the device manufacturers listed on this site. Android is a trademark of Google Inc. Use of this trademark is subject to Google Permissions.

### Modification of Privacy Policy

We have all right for the modification of above Privacy Policy statements without your prior notice or information. If you still have queries regarding out Privacy Policy, then [Contact us](http://xiaomiadvices.com/contact-us/) by filling the form below.
